# **Anatoliy Yastreb**

### **Software Engineer**

https://www.linkedin.com/in/yastreb https://github.com/ayastreb

> anatoliy.yastreb@gmail.com +49 177 7817203

I'm a web software engineer with strong experience in eCommerce who's passionate about complete process of product development - from collecting requirements to deployment and impact analysis.

I enjoy working with smart people, crafting software which brings value to customers, and continuously improving my skills.

#### Skillset

- PHP, Ruby, JavaScript, HTML, CSS
- WebServices (SOAP, REST, oAuth)
- MySQL, ElasticSearch, Redis
- Unit, Integration and End-to-End Testing
- Continuous Integration & Delivery
- Unix server administration

## Experience

### Senior Software Developer at Luxury Fashion Trade GmbH (fashionette.de)

Dusseldorf, Germany, 2013 - 2016

Technologies: Magento, PHP, Laravel, Solr, Varnish, Microservices

Led development team in various projects, including new features implementation, payment methods integration and online shop localization in 16 new countries for Germany's biggest online designer handbags retailer.

### Senior Software Engineer at Magento, X.commerce, Inc. (an eBay company)

Dnipropetrovsk, Ukraine, 2011 – 2013

Technologies: PHP, SOAP WSI, REST, Redis, MongoDB, Gearman

Worked on Magento Core API, performed R&D on Magento 2 API platform. Participated in Magento Connect and Magento GO (SaaS) projects development.

### Web Developer as Independent Contractor

Dnipropetrovsk, Ukraine, 2007 – 2010

Technologies: PHP, JavaScript, AWS, Solr

Implemented various projects, such as <u>DiccionarioLibre.com</u>, <u>ProfileStar.com</u>, <u>MyCubi.com</u>

### Junior PHP Developer at eTek Systems

Dnipropetrovsk, Ukraine, 2006 – 2007

Technologies: PHP, XML, Atom

Worked on international customer's web projects and in-house tools.

#### Education

#### **Udacity**

Tech Entrepreneur Nanodegree, 2015 – 2016

#### National Mining University, Dnepropetrovsk, Ukraine

Bachelor, Management, Economics, 2004 – 2008